const quizQuestions=[
  {question:"What is is the planet closest to the sun?",
  correct_answer:"Mercury",
  incorrect_answers:["Mars", "Venus", "Earth"]
},
{question:"Why doesn’t Mercury have an atmosphere?",
  correct_answer:"It get’s blown away by solar wind",
  incorrect_answers:["It’s too hot", "It's too cold", "No oxygen"]
},
{question:"How fast does Mercury orbit the sun?",
  correct_answer:"47 km/seconds",
  incorrect_answers:["47 km/minute", "47 km/hour", "47 km/day"]
},
{question:"What is Mercury’s radius?",
  correct_answer:"2,440km",
  incorrect_answers:["6,050km", "10,489km", "1,567km"]
},
{question:"What planet is named after the Roman god of love and beauty?",
  correct_answer:"Venus",
  incorrect_answers:["Neptune", "Mars", "Uranus"]
},
{question:"What is Venus's radius?",
  correct_answer:"6,050km",
  incorrect_answers:["2,440km", "10,489km", "1,567km"]
},
{question:"What is the hottest planet?",
  correct_answer:"Venus",
  incorrect_answers:["Mercury", "Mars", "Uranus"]
},
{question:"What is Mercury's surface covered in?",
  correct_answer:"Craters",
  incorrect_answers:["Gas", "Water", "Volcanoes"]
},
{question:"What is Venus's surface covered in?",
  correct_answer:"Volcanoes",
  incorrect_answers:["Gas", "Water", "Craters"]
},
{question:"What is the only planet that rotates counterclockwise?",
  correct_answer:"Venus",
  incorrect_answers:["Earth", "Saturn", "Jupiter"]
},
{question:"What is the distance from Earth to the Sun?",
  correct_answer:"150 million km",
  incorrect_answers:["110 million km", "402 million km", "210 million km"]
},
]


module.exports = {
  quizQuestions
};
